New York State Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors; Records apap315
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Projects and Committees, 1979-2001; Undated; 5; 5.0 cu. ft.
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Meeting Minutes, etc., 1996 December (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 6)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Member Lists, 1997 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 7)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: OASAS Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 8)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: OASAS Regional Office Separation, 1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 9)
  - Chemical Task Force of the M.H.S.C., 1994-1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 10)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Background and Planning materials, 1994 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 11)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Configuration of Developmental Disabilities Services Offices, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 12)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Interim Report, 1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 13)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 14-16)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Project, 1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 17)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Project committee meeting, 1996 May-1996 August (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 18)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot steering committee meeting, 1996 January (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 19)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Steering Subgroup Meeting, 1996 February (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 20)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Subcommittee Meeting, 1996 March (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 21)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Planning letter and draft of "Supports and Services for People with Developmental Disabilities" report, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 22)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Problem Solving, 1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 23)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Survey of County experiences with Developmental Disabilities Services Offices-Draft, Undated (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 24)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Survey of County experiences with Developmental Disabilities Services Offices-Draft, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 25)
  - Commission on 21st Century: "At the Crossroads" report, 2000 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 26)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Children's Mental Health Services Checklist, 1998 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 27)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Committee Recommendations, Final Report, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 28)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Committee Recommendations, Third Draft, Undated (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 29)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Implementation Plan, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 30)
  - Commission on 21st Century: January Meeting, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 31)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Local Stewardship, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 1)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Meeting Advertisements, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 2-3)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Mailing lists for press, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 4)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Photographs, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 5)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Powerpoint presentation, paper and CD, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 6)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Press conference, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 7)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Public testimony, 1998 October (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 8-9)
  - Commission on 21st Century: September Meeting, 1998 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 10)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Subcommittee work, 1996-1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 11)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, commission biographies, 1998 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 12)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, commission members, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 13)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, conference call and correspondence, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 14)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, original contract, 1998 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 15)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, proposal, 1998 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 16)
  - Community service boards matrix, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 17)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) "20 Questions" responses, 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 18-19)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 20-21)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) planning contest-letters and statistics [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 22)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) contest responses [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 23-24)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) planning contest cover forms [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 25)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Prize winners [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 26)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Task force brochure, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 27)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP)- Office of Mental Health, 1979; 1991 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 1)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP)-Report on future of CSPs in New York State, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 2-3)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Grant with Office of Mental Health, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 4-5)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Grant with Office of Mental Health- Audit, 1990; 1993; 1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 6-7)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) task force matrix, Undated (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy-CHAS, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 9-10)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (CHAS) and Division of Housing and Community Renewal (DHCR), 1996 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 11)
  - Conference Committee listing/representation, 1997-2001 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 12)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 13)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Elimination of OMRDD waitlist/NY Cares, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 14)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Meeting minutes, 1994 October (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 15)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Meeting minutes, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 16)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 17)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: New member correspondence, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 18)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Pilot Programs and Partnership Committee, 1996 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 19)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Service Coordination Network software, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 20)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: "Supporting People with Developmental Disabilities and Their Families" OMRDD guide, 1997 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 21)
  - Development Disabilities Committee: Survey materials, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 22)
  - Developmental disabilities matrix, 1993; 1995; 1997 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 23)
  - Disabilities newsletters: Highlights from NYS Assembly and Task Force, 1994 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee-Fall Membership Meeting, 1996 October (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee Matrix, Undated (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1997 January (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 27)
  - Full conference matrix, Undated (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 28)
  - Governor's Office on Information Resource Management-Human Services Workgroup, 1997 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 29)
  - Homeless and Mentally ill veterans workgroup, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 30)
  - Housing Task Force of the M.H.S.C., 1994 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 31)
  - I.S.O. steering committee, 1995 (Box 3 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 32)
  - Kids Oneida: Annual Report, 1999 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 1)
  - Kids Oneida: Background packet, wraparound care, 1992; 1997; 1999 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 2)
  - Kids Oneida: Briefing information and background materials, 1998-1999 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 3)
  - Kids Oneida: Building a plan of care (POC), Undated (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 4)
  - Kids Oneida: Chapter 433 of laws of 1997- Kids Oneida not a special needs plan, Undated (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 5)
  - Kids Oneida: Children's mental healthcare models, New York and Oregon, 1990-1995 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 6)
  - Kids Oneida: Children's system of care/Wraparound service, 2000 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 7)
  - Kids Oneida: "Conducting High Performance Kids Oneida Child and Family Team Meetings", 1996 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 8)
  - Kids Oneida: Contact list and ICAN flow charts, Undated (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 9)
  - Kids Oneida: Covered services, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 10)
  - Kids Oneida: "Crosswalk" between Kids Oneida service codes and NYS Medicaid-State plan services rate codes, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 11)
  - Kids Oneida: Evaluation methodology, 1999 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 12)
  - Kids Oneida: "Family Matters" newsletters, 1991 Fall; 2002 Spring (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 13)
  - Kids Oneida: Final report on integrated delivery systems, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 14)
  - Kids Oneida: Funding/payment policies, 1998; 2000 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 15)
  - Kids Oneida: Innovation Board, 1991-1994; 1997-1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 16)
  - Kids Oneida: Innovation Board, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 17)
  - Kids Oneida: "Lessons Learned-Challenges, Obstacles, and Creative Solutions", 1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 18)
  - Kids Oneida: "Managed Care and Children's Mental Health-Summary of May 1995 State Managed Care Meeting", 1996 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 19)
  - Kids Oneida: Managed care and children's welfare, 1994; 1996 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 20)
  - Kids Oneida: "A Plan for Children, Youth and Family-Mental Health Services in Oneida County", 1985 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 21)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1994; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 22)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1993-1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 23)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1991; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 24)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1996-1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 25)
  - Kids Oneida: Policy recommendations, 2000 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 26)
  - Kids Oneida: Quality Assurance Outcome Measures, 1998 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 27)
  - Kids Oneida: Regulations, 2000 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 28)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Indiana workgroup, 1997 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 29)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Interagency Memorandum of Understanding, 1994 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 30)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, legislation model, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 31)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, stark county, Ohio program, 1996 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 32)
  - Kids Oneida: Steering committee materials, 1995-1997 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 33)
  - Kids Oneida: Tier III workgroup, 1997; 2000 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 34)
  - Kids Oneida: Ventura Planning Model, 1987; 1990 (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 35)
  - Kids Oneida: Welcome Packet, Undated (Box 4 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 36)
  - Local government issues subcommittee, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 1)
  - Mandate Relief Workgroup, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 2)
  - Mental Health Action Network steering committee, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 3)
  - Mental Health Committee, 1993-1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 4)
  - Mental Health Committee Meeting, 1997 September (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 5)
  - Mental Health matrix, Undated (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 6)
  - Missouri Institute of Mental Health, Spring Meeting, St. Louis, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 7)
  - New York Community Trust Grant Proposal, 1990-1993 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 8)
  - New York Community Trust Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 9)
  - New York Community Trust Proposal, 1980; 1989; 1992 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 10)
  - New York Community Trust File, 1991-1993 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 11)
  - New York Community Trust File, 1993-1994 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 12)
  - Nominating committees for 1994 and 1996, 1992 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 13)
  - NYSAC- Welfare, Medicaid, children and families standing committee, 1997-1998; 2004 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 14)
  - Office of Mental Health: Children's Mental Health Advisory Group, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 15)
  - Office of Mental Health-Planning steering committee, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 16)
  - Office of Mental Health-Planning steering committee, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 17)
  - Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities/Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors Partnership Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 18)
  - Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities/Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors Partnership Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 19)
  - Partnership Committee: Pilot subcommittee members, 1996 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 20)
  - Partnership Committee: Pilot subcommittee, 1996 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 21)
  - Policy Resource Center, 1996-1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 22)
  - Rural steering committee, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 23)
  - Rural steering committee, 1995-1996 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 24)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project, 1995-1996 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 25)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Background, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 26)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Notes, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 27-28)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Report- Drafts, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 29)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Report-Drafts and Final, 1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 30)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project, Team One, 1993-1995 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 31)
  - Single state agencies for mental health, 1997 (Box 5 (5-Projects and Committees), Folder 32)
- Managed Care and Special Needs Plans, 1991-2000; Undated; 6; 2.0 cu. ft.
  Managed care, in its most general form, refers to coordination of health services in such a way that quality care is provided, but costs are kept low. Many of the records in this series deal with Medicare issues, of which special needs plans (SNPs) are an important part since they focus effort on particular groups of people with very specific needs. Researchers will find a variety of records such as memos, letters, information packets, and meeting notes covering areas like Medicare financing, managed care in rural areas, strategic planning, technical assistance, and committee work.
  - Adult special needs plans- Financing and public accountability, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 2)
  - Albany County HMO conflicts, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 3)
  - Albany Law Review- Special Needs Plans: Adapting Medicaid Managed Care for Persons with Serious Mental Illness or HIV/AIDs, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 4)
  - Alcohol and substance abuse subcommittee meetings, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 5)
  - Assisted Outpatient Treatment-Volume 1, Initial implementation Sections 1-9, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 6)
  - Assisted Outpatient Treatment-Volume 1, Initial implementation Sections 10-16, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 7)
  - Booklet: "Mental Health Special Needs Plans Request for Information", 1997 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 8)
  - Budget survey/local assistance matches, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 9)
  - Central New York Consortium- Alternative managed care program, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 10)
  - CHPS Consulting, Inc.- Correspondence, meetings, and notes, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 11)
  - Conference managed care meeting, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 12)
  - Consolidated fiscal reform, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 13)
  - "Contracting for Public Mental Health Services" special report, Undated (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 14)
  - County chargebacks- Forensic legislation, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 15)
  - County responses to SNP requests for information, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 16-17)
  - County role in Special Needs Plans selection, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 18)
  - "Effective Public Management of Mental Health Care..…" Report and notes, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 19)
  - Health care financing administration 1115 waiver and award information, 1997 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 20)
  - Historical Medicaid cost and utilization data book, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 21)
  - "Impact of Managed Behavioral Health Services on County-Operated Programs", 1997 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 22)
  - Integrated services and managed care in rural areas, papers and articles, 1997-1998; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 23)
  - International symposium and training seminar on Medicaid Managed Care, SUNY Albany, 1996 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 24)
  - Involuntary Outpatient Treatment, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 25)
  - Managed care basic plan contracts, 1998 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 26)
  - Managed care committee, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 27)
  - Managed care committee, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 28)
  - Managed care committee, 2000 (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 29)
  - Managed care committee meetings, 1997 June; 1997 September (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 30)
  - Managed care committee meetings, 1997 October-1998 October (Box 1 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 31)
  - Managed care consultant services, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 1)
  - Managed care reporting language- financial issues, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 2)
  - Managed care review/Advisory review panel- recommendations, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 3)
  - Managed care working group, 1991 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 4)
  - Managed care working group, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 5-6)
  - Managed mental health care models- California, 1995; 1998 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 7)
  - "Managing care of Schizophrenia"- Four-year study, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 8)
  - "Mandatory Managed Care: Changes in Medicaid Mental Health Services"- Office of Inspector General, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 9)
  - Mathematica study: Care coordination and Medicaid managed care, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 10)
  - "Medicaid Managed Care: Four States' Experiences with Mental Health Carveout Programs", 1999 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 11)
  - Medicaid managed care task force, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 12)
  - Medicaid managed care task force, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 13)
  - Medicaid managed care uniform standards, 1992; 1995-1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 14)
  - Medicaid managed special care, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 15)
  - Medicaid waiver- Alcohol and Substance Abuse Subcommittee, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 16)
  - Medicaid waiver workgroup, 1994 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 17)
  - Memorandums- Managed care priorities, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 18)
  - Mental health liaison group, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 19)
  - Mental Health Weekly, Vol. 10 #25, 2000 June 19 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 20)
  - New York City managed care issues, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 21)
  - "New York State HMOs and their role in Medicaid Managed Care", 1993 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 22)
  - NYSCLMHD- Conference's role in managed care, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 23)
  - Office of Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- Evaluation and monitoring plan demos, 1998 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 24)
  - Other states' health care models- North Carolina and Oregon, 2000 (Box 2 (6-Managed Care and Special Needs Plans), Folder 25)